clientexec.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy

Effective as of April 5, 2014  
These are our Privacy Policies. Every company has terms these are ours. If you have any questions please do not hesitiate to contact us with any concerns. 

At Clientexec, we respect and protect the privacy of visitors to our website, www.clientexec.com (together with the other websites we own and control, the Clientexec Websites”), and our customers who use our on-demand customer service support platform, tools and services offered on the Clientexec Websites (together with the Clientexec Websites, the “Service”). This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how we collect and use visitors’ and customers’ information, particularly personal information, as part of the Service. The information Clientexec collects and uses is limited to the purpose for which customers engage Clientexec and other purposes expressly described in this Policy. Any discussion of your use of the Service in this Policy is meant to include your visits and other interactions with the Clientexec Websites, whether or not you are a user of Clientexec’s billing and support platform. 

### Information You Provide to Us

When you register for the Service, we ask for personal information such as your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information, as well as certain related information like your company name and website name. Clientexec uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use your billing information for any purpose except for credit card processing on Clientexec’s behalf. 

Clientexec may use the personal information you provide to operate the Service and tailor it to your needs, for billing, identification and authentication, to contact and communicate with you about the Service and your use of the Service, send you marketing materials (subject to your opt-out option), for research purposes, and to generally improve the content and functionality of the Service. 

Clientexec may also share your personal information with its third-party service providers (such as its credit card processors and hosting partners) to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and other services we use to operate the Service and maintain a high quality user experience. We do not permit our service providers to use the personal information you provide for their marketing purposes. 

### Information we collect automatically

In addition, Clientexec automatically collects information about your interactions with the Clientexec Websites and Clientexec Services. For example, Clientexec may log information from your computer and browser, such as your IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, browser type, software and hardware attributes, pages you request, and cookie information. By using the Clientexec Services, you are giving Clientexec permission to use and store such information consistent with this privacy policy.

Clientexec uses this information to continuously enhance your user experience. Generally speaking, we use the collected information to improve our products, services and to make sure we are in tune with the aspects of our Website and Services that are key to our customers' and visitors' success. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our servers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to access information when you sign in, store your preferences, to keep you logged in, and to store a limited amount of behavioral data. You can configure your browser to accept or reject these cookie

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website and Service. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to any Clientexec Website.

If you want to learn more about cookies, or how to control or delete them, please visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance. 

### Changes to this Policy

If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an email to the last email address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an email notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our website. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Service. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of our website or Service, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
